tubelittle.com 2007-11-22

# Canadian Pharmacy

What does Generic stand for?

Generic means using a different name for the same ingredients. The contents of the pills are absolutely the same in our generic version and the branded analogue.

Why is your product so cheap?

There is a number of reasons for that. We do not spend anything on marketing, there are no taxes to be paid as the product comes into the country unregistered, the manufacturer is located in an offshore zone and the production costs are way lower. No child labor is used.

Where are your Physicians Licensed?

Our physicians are U.S licensed. We use only board certified physicians and U.S licensed pharmacies.

How do you ship orders?

We can offer 2 shipping methods at the moment: Trackable Courier Service: the packages sent by this postal service can by tracked by the tracking number supplied after the order is shipped. 

| 

To report any abuse or violations of the Canadian Pharmacy service, please send us a message. We will follow up with you and make every effort to trace the origin of the message. Feel free to contact us with any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy. 

**Web Site Information Collection**   
For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes only the consumer's domain name or IP address, but not the e-mail address. Unless otherwise stated on our web site, we collect only the domain name or IP address of visitors to our Web page, the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, user-specific information on what pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and registrations to access portions of the site and their related services or to set up a Canadian Pharmacy account. 

**Use of Web Site Information Collected**   
The information we collect is used to create an aggregate demographic profile of our user base so that we can improve the content and services of our Web site and provide aggregate information to potential advertisers (no individual information is provided to any third-party without your consent), to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor, to notify consumers about updates to our Web site and services, to send visitors our opt-in e-mail newsletter(s) (if requested by the visitor), to provide users with the products and/or services for which they signed-up or registered which may include sending service disruption notices or other service- or product-related information via e-mail, and is not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes without the visitor's consent. 

**Use of Your Email Information**   
Canadian Pharmacy is not an email list rental service and does not rent or sell any email addresses or other contact information that you provide. 

**E-mail and Direct Response Contact**   
All of our direct response methods are opt-in. If you subscribed to our e-mail newsletter(s) but do not want to receive it in the future, please follow the "unsubscribe" instructions contained in the newsletter(s). 

**Postal Address Collection and Use**   
If you supply us with your postal address on-line, we will use it to send you the product for which you provided us your address. If you supply us with your telephone number on-line, we will use it to contact you with information regarding your account, orders your have placed, or with information regarding your inquiry. We **will not** send you information about additional services that we offer and we **will not** rent or sell your contact information to any third parties without your permission. 

**Cookies**   
We, and some of our partners who provide some of the services and products on our site, use cookies to record session information, such as past activity at a site in order to provide better service when visitors return to our site, customize Web page content based on visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends, and to enable access to specific areas on the web site. 

**Changes to Privacy Policy**   
From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in this Privacy Policy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future, we will post the policy changes to our Web site's Privacy Policy page to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site's Privacy Policy page periodically. 

© 2002-2005 Canadian Pharmacy, Inc. All Rights Reserved. 

Last Updated: March 4, 2005 

We accept the following   
payment methods:

| 

| 

Licensed by The College of Pharmacists of British Columbia.

If you have any questions or concerns you can contact the college at 200-1765 West 8th Ave. Vancouver, BC, Canada V6J 5C6 

You may contact us at +1(210) 787-1711, please, keep your order I.D. every time you make a call.
